shobhituniversity.ac.in 2018-06-13

# 

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Shobhit University collects, uses, maintains and discloses
information collected from users (each, a "User") of the shobhituniversity.ac.in website ("Site"). This privacy
policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Shobhit University.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited
to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities,
services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate,
name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information. Users may, however, visit
our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily
submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information,
except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site.
Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical
information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet
service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard
drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set
their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that
some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
Shobhit University may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
        - To process payments
           We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to
           provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the
           extent necessary to provide the service.
        - To send periodic emails
           We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It
           may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides
           to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates,
           related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from
           receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email
           or User may contact us via our Site.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect
against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username,
password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured
communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. Our Site is also in
compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for
Users.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic
aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors

and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We
may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities
on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third
parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners,
suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links
that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from
our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing.
These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and
interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's
own terms and policies.
Changes to this privacy policy
Shobhit University has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise
the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any
changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You
acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become
aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to
this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to
this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site,
please contact us at: Shobhit University shobhituniversity.ac.in
Shobhit University
University Tower, Institutional Area, Pocket-B, Mayur Vihar Phase II, New Delhi - 110 091
01143205500
mail@shobhituniversity.ac.in
This document was last updated on February 22, 2014
